# Daniel Nwaobi Ifechukwude

#### WEB DEVELOPER AND DESIGNER

dannychukz15@gmail.com

in @nwaobidaniel

@CrazyChickenDev

**t** +2348022273025

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm an open-source/blockchain enthusiast, computer engineer, web developer(WordPress Developer) and designer. I'm Project-driven with excellent and strategic knowledge of digital products and services. I've successfully worked with software teams and actualised process improvement through feasible product roadmaps from product development up to product launch.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## NIGERIA DAO AND CREATIVE DAO DEVELOPER AND DESIGNER @HARMONYONE DEC 2021 - JUNE 2022

- I worked with my fellow governors to build the official Harmony Naija DAO website <a href="https://naijadao.one/">https://naijadao.one/</a> which is translated into 4 local languages.
- Created every design asset for the Harmony NaijaDAO Worked with my team to draft the initial proposal with a funding of \$50,000 from Harmony Designed marketing, branding and media assets Technical Training organisation and onboarding of future blockchain builders Offline advocacy and outreach Strategy and brand growth.
- Designed and actively led strategies promoting community growth.
- Onboarded new members onto the DAO Initiated rapid education drive and helpful conversations around blockchain, Defi and NFTs, A poll in the community showed that 25% of people got their first cryptocurrency (\$ONE) or digital asset via the DAO outreaches.
- Facilitated the DAO's first Meet-up in Nigeria on February 19 2022, with over 100 people in attendance and facilitated the second meetup in Lagos Nigeria which was held on April 2, 2022
- Built and designed websites and mobile apps during the governorship span.
- Conducted a Regional Hackathon with over 100 Developer attendees.

#### GRAPHICS AND WEB DESIGNER(WORDPRESS) @ WISPER TELECOMMUNICATION OCT 2021 - JAN 2022

- Wrote modern, performant, maintainable code for a diverse array of clients and internal projects (CONTRACT BASED)
- Created content designs and responsive designs for both the company's social media presence and websites such as its mobile subscription platform <a href="http://mobile.wisper.ng/">http://mobile.wisper.ng/</a> and official website <a href="https://wisper.ng/">https://wisper.ng/</a>
- Developed and maintained programming/interface standards.
- Communicated with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, producers, and clients on a daily basis

## WEB DEVELOPER (WORDPRESS) & DESIGNER @ MUZZLABS MAY 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2021(FULL TIME)

- Built and designed websites and mobile apps during the initial internship span. <a href="https://muzzlab.com/">https://muzzlab.com/</a>
- · Wrote modern, performant, maintainable code for a diverse array of client and internal projects.
- Worked with a variety of different languages, platforms, frameworks, and content management systems such as JavaScript, Node.Js, Gatsby, React, Canva, Azure, and Netlify. - <a href="http://biko.muzzlab.com/">http://biko.muzzlab.com/</a>
- Communicated with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, producers, and clients on a daily basis
- Worked on various designs with other interns in the field using tools such as Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Professional Canva and Figma.
- Worked with products and engineering to develop new docs, changelogs, and any supporting materials Developed supporting technical blogs or articles
- Built responsive and fluid websites for Clients such as http://getpeca.com/ and <a href="http://blog.peca.com/">http://blog.peca.com/</a> using various JavaScript frameworks.
- Worked on other projects such as <a href="http://olajazznft.com/">http://olajazznft.com/</a>, <a href="http://olajazznft.com/">http://olajazznft.com/</a>)</a>

#### **CYBER-SECURITY INTERN @ UNITES**

SEPT 2020 - NOV 2020 (INTERNSHIP)

- Gained simulated experiences in the field of cybersecurity.
- Took up specialization courses in Computer Architecture, Software Engineering and Embedded Systems to broaden my skill set and took up electives in "Cyber Security".
- Manually tested networks, routers, systems and websites in various browsers and mobile devices to ensure cross-browser compatibility, responsiveness and vulnerabilities.
- Built projects related to cybersecurity such as keyloggers and password list generators during the internship.

- Built a strong technical community on my campus by organising events, hackathons, workshops, meetups and the
- Created a community where students can comfortably share their ideas and improve both their tech and soft skills
- Developed and maintained code for event websites primarily using HTML, CSS, Sass and JavaScript
- Interfaced with community individuals and students on a daily basis providing technological expertise

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering (B.Eng.)

July 2016 - 2021

University of Benin, Benin City, Nigeria.

## HARD SKILLS

- Video Editing (Adobe Premiere Pro, Wondershare Filmora)
- Design (Canva, Figma, Illustrator and Photoshop)
- Website Design and Development (HTML&CSS, JavaScript, Node.Js, WordPress, React, Gatsby.Js, RESTful APIs, Git)
- Communications (Slack)
- Documentation (MS Office, Notion, Google Doc/Slide/sheet)

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication Skills
- Organization
- Presentation
- · Problem Solving
- · Conflict Resolution
- Problem Solving
- Critical Thinking

#### **INTERESTS**

- Cryptocurrency
- Blockchain
- Startups
- Programming
- Design
- Entrepreneurship
- Digital Marketing
- SAAS
- Video Games

### **CERTIFICATION S & ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Winner of the "30-day Microsoft Cloud Skills Challenge" Designing and Implementing an Azure Al Solution (June 2020) issued by Microsoft
- First Place WINNER Team "TEAM ARTI" at the "Microsoft Build Cloud Skills Challenge" (June 2020) issued by Microsoft
- GitHub Campus Expert for the University of Benin (2020-2022)
- SEPLAT JV 2020 Scholarship Winner for Students
- "Introduction to Cybersecurity Certification" issued by Cisco Networking Academy
- "ICSI | Cyber-Security Essentials" issued by ICSI, UK (International CyberSecurity Institute)
- "ICSI | Certified Network Security Specialist (CNSS)" issued by ICSI, UK (International CyberSecurity Institute)
- "Cyber Security Foundation Professional Certificate- CSFPC™" issued by CertiProf
- "Networking Academy Learn-A-Thon 2021" issued by Cisco
- "Lifelong Learning" issued by CertiProf
- "Virtual Graduate Internship Program (Cyber Security Operation)" issued by UNITeS Cisco Networking Academy
- Remote Work and Virtual Collaboration Professional Certificate RWVCPC issued by CertiProf